This video introduces the mode and editor update for you.
In the 2025.0 version, we optimized some of the functions of the chess editor.
Next, let's take a look at its update through a file.
Now you can use the shortcut key to quickly open the chess editor window.
Just press the letter O on the keyboard to open the chess editor.
It's the same as the previous version.
When you stop the mouse in the object window,
on the color block of any material,
you can see that it is just a prompt text that uses the color of the chess.
The 2025.0 version is based on this.
It adds the function of directly switching the color of the single color block.
You don't need to open the chess editor to quickly switch the color.
In addition to the fabric, you can also choose the color block below other materials.
For example, the button or name used on the costume.
By clicking on the color block, you can directly switch to the desired color.
Now in the chess editor,
you can directly see the front and side of the fabric.
And based on the need to change or apply color and texture to a specific surface.
First, if you look at the color block of the color block of the color block 2,
you can see that it is divided into three parts.
If you select the back or side of the fabric in the option card,
it will select the same material as the front.
Then you can use the corresponding color blocks in the single-color chess editor
to edit the color and texture of the front, back and side.
As shown in the chess editor,
the texture will be divided by the surface.
From top to bottom is the front, side and back of the fabric.
In addition, if the back or side materials are different from the front,
only the different surfaces will be displayed as separate color blocks.
As shown in the chess editor 3,
only the reverse settings are different from the front in the chess editor 3.
Therefore, it is displayed as two color blocks,
one representing the front and one representing the reverse.
If you want a certain fabric,
all surface colors and textures are the same as the front,
you only need to select the corresponding fabric in the object window and click on it.
Using the same material options as the front,
you will immediately see the chess editor,
the color block in the window and a color block.
From this version,
when you apply color and texture to an independent component,
for example, when you apply color and texture to an independent component,
these components will be displayed in the chess editor in a tree-shaped structure,
which is convenient for viewing and editing.
For example, this is a pig's nose button.
This pig's nose button is created with a separate component.
Next to its name, it will display a small arrow.
When you click on it,
it can display the color blocks of each component separately.
When you click on the color block,
the corresponding part will be displayed in the 3D window.
You can directly change its color and texture.
In the previous version,
when you have set the color of the clothing and apply other materials,
you can only switch to other applications through the control key.
You cannot modify the default way.
From this version,
you can modify the usual application in the user settings
to make the process more efficient.
Go to the main menu at the top,
then click on the user's self-definition,
select other options,
and then find the chess color.
Choose the application you like to apply new materials.
Here, change it to the link option applied to all chess colors.
Then click on the close button to save the settings.
Now let's check whether the new application has been set up.
In the object window,
go to the fabric options card,
then click on the increase button to create a new fabric.
Next, drag this fabric to the pocket panel.
You will see a tool hint behind the mouse light.
It shows that the link option we just selected is activated.
After clicking update,
you will see that the new fabric has been applied to all chess colors
and there is a link.
Please note that even after restarting the software,
this application option will still be used.
Through the optimized chess editor,
you can easily and efficiently create and edit chess costumes.
In the new version,
you can more freely arrange the materials.
When you want to keep the original fabric,
you can also change the pattern of the fabric.
And when you finish other fabrics,
there is a simpler way to achieve it.
First, let's switch to the cherry blossom release mode.
At this time, you can see that the dress's large fabric has been finished.
In general, for patterned fabrics,
you may want to keep the current pattern result
after making the pattern in the reference text.
We can now separate the other fabrics to make the pattern.
First, switch to the denim fabric to adjust the pattern settings.
The design is transparent from the front to the back.
Long press the original pattern function.
You can see that there are two patterns currently supported.
They are the front and back fabrics of the pattern.
You can switch to the front fabric of the pattern.
Just do the pattern on the front fabric.
After the pattern is completed,
let's switch to you pattern fabric.
You can see that the pattern of the pattern
has retained the original pattern result.
In addition to the above situation, this function can also help you to achieve a faster
processing speed when you only need to assemble a certain fabric with multiple pieces of clothing.
I hope this function can help you to process more freely and flexibly.
In the new version, the UV editing mode has become a UV editor.
This can help you to reduce the operation steps and optimize the workflow.
In addition, a new UV expansion function has been added.
It can display and prepare the texture of the back and sides of the fabric.
Next, let's see how to operate it together.
In the UV editor window, find the UV coordinate position of the leather fabric.
You can see that the front and back and sides of the leather are different.
Select all the sheets of leather applied.
Find the UV expansion in the property editor.
Below the UV expansion, you can see the options of the back and sides.
When selecting the back, the selected sheet will display the texture of the leather back.
When selecting the side, the selected sheet will display the texture of the leather side.
If you find that after selecting the UV expansion, the UV editor does not display the back and side texture.
Please check if the thick texture surface of the 3D window has been opened.
Then, select all sheets to automatically fill in the UV.
Next, let's see how to prepare the back and side texture of the leather.
In the tool bar on the right side of the UV editor, click on the back and side texture of the leather.
As before, you can set the storage path and UV area of the UV texture in the back and side texture window.
And select the texture type you need.
Click Save after setting it up.
This is the saved UV texture.
Please note that when downloading the customized clothing file in the lower version,
the UV expansion default is closed.
This is to keep the existing UV layout.
If you force open it, the previously hidden UV may appear by accident,
thereby destroying the expected UV layout.
If the applied fabric has the same back and side texture,
and only the side is different, you can only select the side.
This function can be applied to 3D files of wool, leather, and other fabrics.
If this type of file needs to be exported as FBX color file and edited in the third-party software,
then the performance of the back and side texture will be very useful.
Let's see FBX in more detail.
You can create different elevated layer using a tool linked to the back and side texture.
If the ABX load area is used,
the UV texture of the back and side texture can be adjusted,
and the colorization of the back and side texture can be changed.
The Seoul international uma 1080pata 2 Night camera is working well.
Press the button to see if you want to change the number or speed of the Pedal.
If the photo you want to play is running on the back and side texture,
the
back and side texture will be set to alternate.